Monokamaru's Marutto Channel
Hello everyone, this is Kazami.
Yes, that's right, this time
I'd like to introduce some of my recent purchases!
Yikes, a futon!
Hey, um, well...
I'm not so much of a, uh...
I'm a person who likes to save money.
I'm not the type of person who buys things without hesitation.
But recently I bought some clothes and went on a trip.
I'd like to introduce some of the things I bought there.
Let's go!
Seino
Triangle
What should I do first?
First, let's start with clothes.
I say clothes, but let's start with accessories.
Here's the first one.
There you go!
Do you think it will look like this?
This...
I think it was popular for a while, but you tie it around your waist like this.
Then you tie a ribbon around the waist and fasten it, a little like an apron.
Just by attaching it to your pants, you can make it look fashionable like a layered coordinate.
Also, since it comes with a pattern, it can be used for, for example, an outfit that's too simple.
For example, if you feel that this outfit is too simple, or that the top of the dress is a little too "moo moo moo moo", you can just attach this to your pants and it will look more stylish.
I think it's cute even if you put it on a skirt.
I bought it because I thought it was so easy to wear, and I'd always wanted one, but Emma and Aya had one.
That's why it's in the sky.
I've always wanted to buy one, but Emma and Aya had one like it.
I'm glad I bought it, because I can use it.
I bought it at FreakSmart FreakSmart.
I bought it at FreakSmart.
And one more thing. It's not clothes.
It's a hat!
It's cute, a little brownish, and shiny.
I went looking for something to accentuate my fall clothes and accessories.
The back is frosted, like this.
I made a frango, but you can put it on.
It's also cute just pulled down like this.
I asked the sales clerk about it.
I've never done it before.
I haven't done it yet.
Like a ribbon knot.
She said it would be cute.
I want this so bad!
It's not what I'm looking for.
I didn't go looking for this.
I didn't go looking for this, but the hat is cute too.
For example...
I used to wear in the summer.
A white T-shirt and a floral skirt.
I was wearing a floral skirt.
I was wearing a white T-shirt and a floral skirt
It's like fall all at once, isn't it?
It's been hot this year, hasn't it?
There are cold days, but
but overall, it's a little warmer.
It's still like the continuation of summer.
But it's October in terms of the month
You want to make it look a little like autumn, don't you?
But it's too hot for that.
Just by putting this on a T-shirt skirt, you can make it look a little more like fall.
just by putting this on a T-shirt skirt, you can make it look a little more like fall
I thought it would be really easy to use.
So I thought it would be easy to use.
The sales clerk recommended it to me and I bought it.
I bought it!
I thought it was cute when I saw it.
I thought it was cute, like a beige hat without the sparkling string.
I thought it would be cute if it was just a knit hat.
The clerk said so...
She said, "I think this one would probably look really good on you.
When I put it on, I thought it was cute.
I look a little like an acorn...
It's cute!
I bought it. I bought this at Castanet, by the way.
There was another cute pair of brown pants at Castanet.
I'm trying to be cool.
Not pants?
There were some pants, but I thought it would be too much if I bought those too.
I'm not going to buy them, but I want to buy them.
So the clothes were pretty good.
So your clothes were pretty good.
Also, I went shopping with Emma Sakurai the other day.
I mean, we went to Atami for shopping.
We often play with used trios.
Yuna and I also eat a lot of meals together.
Yuna eats a lot too.
So we often go out to eat together.
Emma and I have never gone out alone.
The day before the lesson, we were on a tight schedule.
I said, "Are you free tomorrow?
I said, "Yes, I'm free.
I said, "What do you say we go out for fun? I said...
And he's like, "Oh, no! And then...
I mean, the city's fine if you want to go at the same time.
But I was in the mood to go somewhere far away.
I said I wanted to go to Atami or Hakone.
Atami?
I had already done some research and found some restaurants and foods I wanted to eat.
I thought "Atami", so I bought something at Atami.
Let me introduce what I bought in Atami.
First of all
There is an unmanned accessory shop called Okuoku in the shopping street in front of Atami station.
There is an unmanned accessory shop in front of Atami station, and they have a lot of accessories, but everything is 200 yen.
I don't wear rings much these days, but when I wear one, it makes a big difference.
I've recently started collecting rings, and although I can't afford to buy expensive ones
I can't afford to buy expensive ones, but I bought some lattices, for 200 yen, and some mornings.
I bought some mornings.
I can't afford to buy so many.
Cute!
First of all, I wanted to do something safe.
Oh, I want to do this.
I don't want that one. It's an azab.
Silver ring.
It's easy to use, isn't it?
I had a few rings that were a little too simple and cute, but I was a little too much of a fan of the zig-zag pattern.
I wanted a ring with a bit of a feminine feel.
I wanted a ring with a feminine feel.
I wanted a ring with a more feminine look, so I got this one and this one.
Jajan!
ring
This one, here...
This is what it looks like.
And in the middle, there are two big pendants like this.
like this pendant in the middle.
It's cute when I put it on.
You can see my stubby fingers. It's embarrassing.
It's cute. It's cute. I bought it because I thought it would add a little accent.
My fingers are pretty thin.
So it's hard to find a ring that's a little big and fits.
I can't stay there.
I had to do a lot of checking.
I also have one more ring that matches Emma's.
Ta-da!
This is a pretty big one.
It's silver with a flower-like design.
It's a silver ring with a flower-like design.
It's so cute!
It's a little big, but...
The color of the flower is yellow.
It has that color.
It's got that...
It's got flowers in it.
I thought it was cute.
I thought about matching it with Emma's, but I thought this one would be easier to use.
So I decided to go with this one, but it's still cute.
This one is a little thicker, so I'm thinking of putting it on my thumb or something.
I think I'll put it on my thumb.
The first one I introduced, the tiny ring, is quite thin, so my middle finger won't fit in it.
It's a little too loose for my middle finger, so I thought I'd use my ring finger.
This is the ring I bought.
And there is another ring that I bought.
Before...
We went on a family trip to Atami in January to celebrate my father's 60th birthday.
I found a tiny general store called "New Atami" at that time.
My brother told me about it, and it was really cute.
But the last time I went there, the prices were quite expensive.
Each item is handmade.
Last time, there was something I wanted to buy, but I didn't want to spend 600 yen.
This is a key chain.
I have it on my pen case at school.
I bought a key chain.
But I went there once more, didn't I?
This time
I still wanted to buy it.
so I bought it!
Ta-da-da-da!
So cute!
Maybe it's an ashtray?
I don't know...
but even if you use it as a small container
I think it's really cute.
For example, you could put rings in it.
For example, you could put the rings you just bought in it.
or a little lipstick?
Something like that.
I thought it would be really cute in a room.
I was looking at it last time.
I was looking at it last time, but...
I didn't buy it.
I went back a second time.
I wanted to buy it.
I thought I should buy it.
Let's buy it
I bought it
I didn't remember
The last time I went on an attached trip
I bought it for my brother when we were on our last trip together.
He and I are matching now!
Yay!
but...
I want to use it as a container.
the picture is so cute!
you will love you!
Souvenir Store
You love you
Souvenir
I paint the sea
I met you I am happy
I can use this alone
Someday
I hope you all will visit Atami when you go there.
It's become one of my favorite places.
Mu Atami
It's a little bit small, so it's a great place to eat.
It's a little bit small.
If too many people come
I think it's too much for the store owner
I think I'll be your companion.
So we'll split the days.
and watch your breathing.
I'm sure you'll have a great time.
Really cute.
And the knit hats and stuff are cute too.
And clothes.
They also have T-shirts and stuff like that.
It's become one of my favorite stores.
The pieces are a bit expensive, but the colors and designs are so cute, so please give them a try.
And that's the end of the introduction of this article.
There are only 4 kinds.
3 days
And I'll introduce one more piece.
I didn't buy this one.
I didn't buy this.
A birthday present.
You got it, didn't you?
One of the members asked me what I wanted.
They asked me what I wanted.
I wanted some perfume.
I don't know much about perfume.
I've never put it on.
It made my stomach turn.
I've never worn perfume.
I've never worn perfume, but...
I know a lot of the older members...
I've seen some of them wearing it.
I thought it was nice.
I thought I'd look for a course I like.
I think there's a shop called IAM
I think there's a store called
I'm thinking of going to the IAM store.
Why don't you let me out?
On a day like that...
What kind of smells do you like?
I like this one.
I got it as a birthday present.
Wow!
This is the first time
I bought such a nice perfume!
It's I Am's Tiptor 8.
It was very popular when I went to the store.
This is probably the 50ml.
30 ml.
But they said they were out of the 50ml one.
But I was told that they were out of the 50ml.
It smells so good!
I wonder what it is?
It's so cute!
It's amazing!
This one's cute, too.
I don't know. It smells so fresh.
There's the smell of flowers in it.
Spring
It smells like a very fresh morning.
But after that, there's a sweet smell of flowers.
It's a nice touch.
I thought I could make it smell like a girl.
I think it smells really good if I can do it.
I bought it, but...
There are so many different smells.
I couldn't keep track of them all.
What? What's this?
And a second one, too.
A second?
There is a second one, isn't there?
The main smell is this, but then there's this other smell that you get afterwards.
I don't know.
I said, "Sis.
I didn't know what it was, but it smelled so good.
So I asked her to buy it for me.
Take care of the water a little bit.
It's so pretty, I want to put it on display.
I want to put it on display.
I asked her about her perfume.
I'm going to be using this perfume a lot at the upcoming award shows and live performances.
Oh!
Please come to the benefit parties to see how much perfume I can use, as I said on the Rejuvenation Channel.
I hope you don't smell it too much.
And finally...
No?
Oh, look.
This one's really pretty, too.
This one's pretty, too.
But I don't think I'll ever use it.
It's so cute, I want to keep it.
I want to save it.
But I want to use it.
I want to use it.
I'll use it.
So this time
Introduction of Purchased Items
I would like to introduce my recent purchases.
I'll be bringing you
I'll show you what I like and where I bought it.
I'm glad we're matching, but it's fun to have a maximum of matching.
These are cute, but they're all full of acorns.
There are so many acorns!
Please check out the ones you like!
So, please click the "Good" button, leave a comment, and subscribe to the channel!
After this, I'm going to play with my kids.
So I'll be hungry like this.
Have fun!
Bye bye!